gaijinpot.com 2014-02-10

# Privacy Policy ‹ GaijinPot Jobs

### 1\. Definitions and Parties

The treatment of the information collected through the use of [jobs.gaijinpot.com](https://jobs.gaijinpot.com/) and through GaijinPot Jobs Partner Sites, herein collectively referred to as the ‘site’, is governed by the present privacy policy.  
This is a legal document between the administrator of GaijinPot Jobs, GPlus Media Co., Ltd. herein referred to as ‘GPlus’, and the users of the site herein referred as to ‘users’.

GPlus is committed to protecting the privacy of the site’s users. This commitment is demonstrated in the structure of the database, programming, and the use of encrypted pages for the transfer of sensitive data.

GPlus is the unique owner of the information collected through the site. We do not sell, share or lease the information in other ways than stated in this Privacy Policy.

By using this site, users show their binding acceptance to the present Privacy Policy.

Users are assumed to use this site at their own discretion and responsibility.

In this document users will find about:

  * Personal information and collection process
  * Use of information
  * Disclosure of personal information
  * Personal information protection measures
  * Users’ ability to modify their personal information

Should you have any question, feel free to send us an inquiry.

### 2\. Links

This site contains links to external sites administrated by third parties. GPlus shall not be held responsible for any Privacy Policy issues related to such external sites.  
When redirected to an external site, users should check the applying Privacy Policy.

### 3\. Personal Information

This site’s content is visible to everybody. However, in order to use certain features, users have to register providing the following personal information:

  * Email address
  * Password

In order to build resumes to apply to jobs, users have to provide the following personal information:

  * Name
  * Birth date
  * Gender
  * Nationality
  * Country and state of residence
  * Closest train station
  * Phone number
  * Visa status

Other non-personal information is required to build a resume such as: 

  * Language skills
  * Education level
  * Career level

When posting their resumes, users can control the level of visibility by choosing to:

  1. a. keep their resume private. Employers will never be able to look at these resumes unless submitted directly by the users.
  2. b. make their resumes open to resume search. Employers will be able to look at such resumes and send invitations. However, users’ personal information and last employer information will not be disclosed.

The level of visibility of a resume can be changed at any time by the user.

### 4\. Other Information Sources

In order to enhance the quality of the site and to facilitate the users’ navigation, GPlus collects other information from users’ traffic through the following methods:

  * Log files
  * Cookies
  * Web beacons

### 5\. Use of Information

In accordance with the selected level of visibility chosen by each user as explained in section 2, GPlus will use the information for the following purposes only:

  * For statistical research
  * To ask users to update their information
  * To identify users using the site’s features including resume posting and job application
  * To contact users by email about the site’s updates
  * To contact users by email about available positions
  * To enable employers to use the resume search

### 6\. Disclosure of Personal Information

Users’ personal information is never disclosed to third parties except in the following cases:

  * If ordered by governmental authorities
  * If it is required by law

### 7\. Information Protection Measures

GPlus’ s internal privacy and security policies are reviewed on a regular basis. GPlus staff receive training on information protection measures.  
Furthermore, in order to protect the information from unauthorized use, system crash or viruses, GPlus has implemented the following measures:

  * Data is stored in a data center requiring a biometric authentication and ID cards
  * Access is restricted to authorized personnel
  * Firewall
  * Linux environment
  * SSL Certificate

Internally, only authorized personal are allowed to consult personal information for specific purposes.

### 8\. Modification of Personal Information

Users can modify or delete their personal information anytime.  
Should you need assistance to do so, please contact GPlus through contact form.

### 9\. Modification of Privacy Policy

GPlus reserves the right to modify the present Privacy Policy without prior notice. By their continued use of the site, users are expected to agree with the revised Privacy Policy available on this same page.

### 10\. Date

The present Privacy Policy shall become effective from April 1, 2009.
